

Mahmoud Mayaleh

Computer Engineer

www.mayaleh.com in Mahmoud Mayaleh

WHO AM I?

Computer engineer specializing in full stack development.

Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects and console applications. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including C++, C#, HTML5, CSS, and SQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering,

Ostim Technical University ∂ 09/2020 - 07/2024 | Ankara, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Internship, Ostim Technical University
- IT department
07/2022 - 03/2023 | Ankara, Turkey

Internship, Vedubox company ∂
01/2022 - 02/2022 | Ankara, Turkey

SKILLS

- Project management
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Fast learner

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C++ C# CSS HTML

Python

INTERESTS

- Photoshop editing
- AutoCAD Designing

LANGUAGES

English

C1

Turkish • • • • •

Α2